&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在您了解了语法糖层是什么样子的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So now you understand what the syntactic sugar layer looks like,
但是让我们揭开被子，看看下面，然后
but let's peel back the covers, look underneath, and
了解它所在的原型系统实际上是如何工作的。
find out how the prototype system that it's layered on top of actually works.
与我教给你的其他东西完全一样，最好理解
Exactly the same as everything else I've taught you, it's better to understand
这些系统比只有，嗯，我不知道它是如何工作的，这是一个黑匣子。
these systems than to just have, well, I don't know how it works, it's a black box.
或者更糟的是，有一个完全错误的心理模型。
Or worse, have a totally wrong mental model for it.
所以我们想看看原型系统是如何工作的，并且
So we wanna look at how the prototype system works, and
具体地说，它是如何用JavaScript实现类系统的。
specifically how its used to implement class systems in JavaScript.
我要做的第一个观察是，我们程序中存在的对象
First observation I would make is that objects that exist in our programs that we
可以看到我们创造的或与之互动的东西，
can see and that we create or that we interact with,
它们总是由这些所谓的构造函数调用创建的。
they're always created by these so-called constructor calls.
您可能还记得我们在讨论这个关键字时，我说的new in
You might remember in our discussion of this keyword that I said that new in
函数调用的前面是构造函数调用。
front of a function call is a constructor call.
这和说有一个构造函数不是一回事，
That is not the same thing as saying there's a constructor,
简单地说，基本上是为了
it is to simply say that that is basically for
当您在函数调用前使用new时，缺少更好的术语
lack of a better term when you use new in front of a function call it's
构造一个用于该函数调用的绑定的对象。
constructing an object to be used for this binding of that function call.
这就是物体的来源。
So that's where objects come from.
它们通过这些构造函数调用的new来。
They come via new from these constructor calls.
人们常说，在构建这些新对象的过程中
And it is often said that in that process of constructing these new objects
它是基于构造器的原型来创建对象的。
that it's making that object based on the constructor's prototype.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这个短语的基础就是我不得不提出的问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That phrase based on is what I have to take issue with.
所以我会暂时偏离或者
So I'm gonna just for a moment diverge from or
不要再谈论JavaScript了。
go down from talking about JavaScript.
我会先摘下JavaScript帽子，然后
I'll take off the JavaScript hat for a moment, and
我想更多地谈谈阶级理论的基础。
I wanna talk more about the foundations of class theory.
就好像你在CS101他们会教你所有的课程，
As if you were in CS101 and they were gonna teach you all about classes,
他们会向你解释什么课程？
what would they explain to you about classes?
好的，第一个，最常见的比喻来描述
Well, number one, the most common metaphor to describe the difference between
类和实例是类是事物的抽象模式。
a class and an instance is that a class is the abstract pattern for a thing.
就像一张蓝图。
It's like a blueprint.
这个例子就像建筑师拿着蓝图建造东西一样。
And the instance is like when an architect takes the blueprint and builds the thing.
这是字面上具体的东西。
It's the literal concrete thing.
所以我们有蓝图，抽象，计划，这就是班级。
So we have blueprint, abstract, plan, that's the class.
我们有物理的，具体的，物体，这就是实例。
We have physical, concrete, object, that's the instance.
这是最常见的隐喻。
That's the most common of those metaphors.
现在这个比喻中，不管你是否意识到，
Now in that metaphor, whether you realize it or not,
有些东西在暗示着你。
there's something being implied to you.
你开始意识到，你正在内化，
And you're picking up on and you're internalizing,
就像其他任何曾经做过面向类编码的人一样。
just like anybody else that's ever done class-oriented coding has.
而且面向类的编码从根本上来说是一种复制操作。
And it is that class-oriented coding is fundamentally a copy operation.
当我说这些的时候，喜欢上课的人会
And I get push back on this a lot, when I say this, people that like classes will
反击，他们会说，不，但是。
push back and they say, no, no, no, but, but, but, but.
他们会指出很多其他语言的例子
And they'll point to lots of other examples of languages where it's
不完全是那样。
not exactly that.
事实是没有一个具体的标准
The truth is that there is no one specific standard for
类设计模式的真正含义。
what the class design pattern really is.
有很多不同的。
There's a lots of different ones.
但同样真实的是，大多数编写JavaScript的人都是第一个
But it is also true that the majority of people that write JavaScript, the first
当他们看到类似类的东西时，是在Java或C+这样的语言中。
time they ever saw something like a class was in a language like Java or C++.
因此，Java和C+的类风格对思想和
So Java and C++'s flavor of classes is heavily influential in the mind and
人们对班级的心理模型。
mental model that people have about classes.
当然，我的CS程序做的都是Java和C+，这是唯一
Certainly my CS program did all Java and all C++, that's the only
不管我在学校里有多少年，他们在课堂上都是这么做的。
class learning they did for the entire however many years I was in school.
而且我认为我绝对不是唯一一个通过以下方式来使用JavaScript的人
And I think I'm definitely not the only one who comes to JavaScript by way of
我称之为更传统的面向类的语言。
what I would call more traditional class-oriented languages.
当我们说复制的这个想法，当我们用CS程序教它的时候
And when we say this idea of copying, and when we teach it in a CS program
如果有复制行为，那就意味着什么。
as if there's a copy behavior, that means something.
它意味着我们的期望，
It means something about our expectations,
我们甚至潜意识中对我们认为代码会做什么的期望。
our even subconscious expectations about what we think the code will do.
所以这就是为什么这个比喻意味着没有你的复制关系
So here's why that metaphor implies that copy relationship without you
甚至可能知道。
potentially even knowing it.
让我们想象一下，你为一座建筑绘制了蓝图，
Let's imagine that you draw up the blueprints for a building and
然后你去建大楼。
then you go build the building.
建筑师建造，他设计它，然后有人去建造它。
The architect builds, he designs it and then somebody goes and builds it.
现在，如果你回到蓝图上擦掉一堵墙会发生什么？
Now, what would happen if you came back to the blueprints and you erased a wall?
那堵墙会从楼里消失吗？
Is that wall gonna disappear from the building?
不，那太疯狂了，对吧？
No, that would be crazy, right?
那真的很奇怪。
That would be really weird.
如果你去了那栋楼
What happens if you went to the building and
你安装了一扇不在原计划中的新窗户？
you installed a new window that wasn't in the original plans?
它会神奇地出现在蓝图上吗？
Does it magically show up on the blueprint?
原因是因为蓝图和
The reason is because the relationship that existed between the blueprint and
如果你愿意，这座建筑在瞬间就存在了，
the building existed for the split second, if you will,
它正在被实例化。
that it was being instantiated.
蓝图中的特征被复制到
The characteristics from the blueprint were copied into
真正的建筑，然后这种关系就不复存在了。
the real building and then the relationship ceased to exist.
你听懂了吗？
You follow me?
所以隐喻本身和
So that metaphor in and of itself and
我们在实例化时思考我们正在做的事情的方式。
the way we think about what we're doing when we're instantiating.
当您创建类的实例时，
When you make an instance of a class,
你得到的心智模型是我的实例是所有这些行为的副本。
the mental model that you're getting is my instance is a copy of all those behaviors.
他们是遗传的，这就是复制。
They're inherited, and that's copying.
说到继承，
Speaking of inherited,
当你开始谈论班级时，你立即开始谈论家长和
when you start talking about classes you immediately start talking about parent and
子类，以及所有关于继承的东西。
child classes, and all what inheritance is about.
继承从根本上来说也是一个复制操作。
An inheritance is also fundamentally a copy operation.
最常用来描述遗传的隐喻是遗传
The metaphor that's most often used to describe inheritance is the genetic
比喻。
metaphor.
现在我有一个儿子，他八岁了，当他被创造的时候，
Now I have a son, he's eight years old and when he was created,
他拿到了我的DNA拷贝
he got a copy of my DNA.
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：他现在作为一个完全独立的人存在。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: He now exist as an entirely independent person.
如果他在今晚的棒球比赛中摔断了腿，我的腿就不会断了。
If he breaks his leg in his baseball game tonight, my leg is not gonna get broken.
如果有一天我掉了头发，希望他真的掉了头发。
And if I lose my hair someday, hopefully he does lose his hair.
我们是截然不同的人，但是
We are distinct people, but
我们在创造的那一刻就有一种关系，那是一种复制关系。
we had a relationship at the moment of creation that was a copy relationship.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：事实上，即使你想到很多语言，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: As a matter of fact, even when you think about many languages,
解释器，编译器，将实现类，
interpreters, compilers, will implement classes,
实际上，由于性能原因，他们会将其展平。
they will actually flatten them for performance reasons.
它们将从字面上复制到实例中，因为它的速度要快得多
They will literally copy down into the instance, cuz it's much faster for
实例具有对函数的引用，而不是必须查找一些
the instance to have a reference to the function instead of having to look up some
动态类层次结构链。
dynamic class hierarchy chain.
只有当存在相对多态性时，它们才维护类层次结构链。
They only maintain the class hierarchy chain when there's relative polymorphism.
这叫做虚拟表。
It's called a virtual table.
这是来自C+的，好吗？
That's from C++, okay?
所以在所有可能的方式你切片这个，
So in all possible ways that you slice this,
类隐含的关系是复制关系。
the relationship that is implied by classes is a copy relationship.
所以我们把我们的谈话堆回到
And so we pop the stack of our conversation back to
幻灯片上的这句话，以及那句话的基础。
this statement on the slide, and that phrase based on.
当我们说构造函数调用是基于其原型创建对象时，
When we say a constructor call is making the object based on its prototype,
我们在我们的心理模型中说，构造器是
we're saying in our mental model that the constructor is
在实例中制作原型的副本。
making a copy of the prototype in the instance.
只是有个小细节，
Except there's a little tiny detail,
也就是说，JavaScript根本不做任何复制。
which is JavaScript doesn't do any copying at all.
事实上，要正确描述构造函数调用时发生的情况
As a matter of fact, to properly describe what is happening when a constructor call
创建一个对象，而不是基于构造函数的原型。
makes an object, it doesn't make it based on the constructor's prototype.
它使它与原型相联系。
It makes it linked to the prototype.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：现在有很多人和我争论，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now there are many that have argued with me and
说，它不同意我和
said, it have disagreed with me and
说复制和链接是没有区别的。
said copying versus linking is a distinction without difference.
没有区别，没关系，只有两个不同的方面
There's no difference there, it doesn't matter, there are just two different sides
同样，链接只是复制的动态形式。
of the same thing, linking is just the dynamic form of copy.
我非常不同意。
And I couldn't disagree more.
链接和复制不仅仅是同一枚硬币的两个不同面，
Linking and copying are not just two different sides of the same coin,
它们是完全的，根本的，截然相反的。
they are completely and fundamentally and diametrically opposite to each other.
并且它们完全改变了您对系统的期望所基于的内容
And they completely change what your expectation of a system is based on
无论你的心智模型是关于复制，还是
whether your mental model is all about copying, or
你的心智模型都是关于链接的。
your mental model is all about linking.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：你使用的心智模型很重要
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It matters what mental model you're using for
期望，因为当程序中断时，为什么会中断？
expectation because when the program breaks, why did it break?
它坏了是因为你的想法和你的想法有分歧，
It broke because you had a divergence between what you were thinking,
你的心智模型，以及系统实际上在做什么。
your mental model, and what the system was actually doing.
如果你认为复制和它做的是链接，猜猜会发生什么。
If you're thinking copying and it's doing linking, guess what is going to occur.
不是也许，会发生，虫子。
Not maybe, will occur, bugs.
因为你的心智模型偏离了它的工作方式。
Cuz your mental model diverges from the way it works.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以我对尝试
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So I have a problem with this whole notion of trying to take
一个类系统，它从根本上是复制的，设计模式的
a class system, which is fundamentally copy, the design pattern's
从根本上复制，并将其放在不进行复制的语言之上。
fundamentally copy, and put it on top of a language that doesn't do copies.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它不合适。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It doesn't fit.
我们在制作过程中遇到了这么多麻烦也就不足为奇了
And it shouldn't be surprising that we've had so much trouble making
JavaScript的外观和行为就像一种与类相关的语言。
JavaScript look and feel and behave like a class-related language.
它们只是不适合在一起。
They're just not designed to fit together.
至少在你从Java或C+得到的心智模型中是这样的。
At least in the mental model you get from say a Java or a C++.